{
  "categories": [],
  "description": "What is the chemical name of this ion?",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "rules": {
    "factor": 1,
    "caseMatters": true
  },
  "questions": [
    {"answer": "H+1","question": "Hydrogen"}, 
    {"answer": "Na+1","question": "Sodium"}, 
    {"answer": "K+1","question": "Potassium"}, 
    {"answer": "Mg+2", "question": "Magnesium"}, 
    {"answer": "Ca+2","question": "Calcium"}, 
    {"answer": "F-1","question": "Flouride"}, 
    {"answer": "Cl-1",  "question": "Chloride"}, 
    {"answer": "Br-1","question": "Bromide"}, 
    {"answer": "I-1","question": "Iodide"}, 
    {"answer": "O-2",  "question": "Oxide"}, 
    {"answer": "OH-1",  "question": "Hydroxide"}, 
    {"question":"Cesium","answer":"Cs+1"}, 
    {"question":"Silver","answer":"Ag+1"}, 
    {"question":"Zinc","answer":"Zn+2"}, 
    {"question":"Barium","answer":"Ba+2"}, 
    {"question":"Chlorate","answer":"ClO3-1"},
    {"question":"Cadmium","answer":"Cd+2"}, 
    {"question":"Cynaide", "answer":"CN-1"}, 
    {"question":"Dichromate", "answer":"Cr2O7-2"}, 
    {"question":"Scandium", "answer":"Sc+3"},
    {"question":"Ammonium","answer":"NH4+1"},
    {"question":"Lithium","answer":"Li+1"},
    {"question":"Aluminum","answer":"Al+3"},
    {"question":"Sulfate","answer":"SO4-2"},
    {"question":"Carbonate","answer":"CO3-2"},
    {"question":"Acetate","answer":"C2H3O2-1"},
    {"question":"Chromate","answer":"CrO4-2"},
    {"question":"Phosphate","answer":"PO4-3"},
    {"question":"Nitrate","answer":"NO3-1"},
    {"question":"Sulfide","answer":"S-2"},
    {"question":"Arsenic","answer":"As+3"},
    {"question":"Iodate","answer":"IO3-1"},
    {"question":"Silicate","answer":"SiO3-2"},
    {"question":"Arsenate","answer":"AsO4-3"},
    {"question":"Rubidium","answer":"Rb+1"},
    {"question":"Strontium","answer":"Sr+2"},
    {"question":"Phosphide","answer":"P-3"},
    {"question":"Nitride","answer":"N-3"},
    {"question":"Carbide","answer":"C-4"},
    {"question":"Peroxide","answer":"O-2"},
    {"question":"Hydride","answer":"H-1"},
    {"question":"Selenide","answer":"Se-2"},
    {"question":"Telluride","answer":"Te-2"}
  ],

  "quizLength": 24,
  "title": "Ions Quiz",
  "url": ""
}